# KATELYN MICHALOVE

Product Designer

katelynmichalove@gmail.com

615-613-5617

katelynmichalove.com

### **SUMMARY**

I am a Product Designer with an instinct for leading research studies and implementing solutions in both low and high fidelity prototypes. I want to combine these skills and continue to grow in a position that requires user research, design, and product vision.

# **SKILL SET**

UX/UI Design
Visual Design
User Research
Market Research
Usability Testing
Information Architecture
Branding
Prototyping
Frontend Development

# **TOOLS**

Adobe Creative Suite
Optimal Workshop
Usability Hub
Lookback, Loom
Omnigraffle, Axure
Sketch, Figma
InVision, Marvel
Git & GitHub
HTML, CSS
Jira

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Sunbelt Rentals / Product Designer**

July 2019 - present Charlotte, NC

- Research- Led usability testing and interviewing for both internal and external facing mobile and desktop applications. Led card sorting exercise to redesign navigation.
- UX Design User Stories, User Flows, Wireframing, prototyping, testing.
- Visual Design- Iconography to match the current branding. High fidelity mockups for new website features.

#### Freelance / Product Designer

August 2018- July 2019 Remote / Seattle, Washington

- UX Design- Competitive Analysis, User Stories, User Flows, Wireframing, Prototyping, User Testing
- Visual Design- Branding, High Fidelity Mockups, Prototyping, User Testing
- Frontend with Webflow and embedded HTML. See the website here
- Remote meetings to discuss branding, design direction, scope, and timeframe.

#### **Procter and Gamble / Process Engineer**

June 2017 - July 2018 Sacramento, CA

- Led troubleshooting group through the stages of problem solving from exploration to documentation
- Designed documents and a wellness program according to branding style guide.

## **EDUCATION**

University of Tennessee / 2017 / BA Chemical Engineering

**Bloc** / 2019 / UX Design Apprenticeship

Remote program focused on designing 5 projects with consistent feedback through mentorship, grading team, and daily design critiques.